<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Shell Venom</title>
    <link>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Shell Venom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:34:13 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Download IPA Files For Security Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/how-to-download-ipa-files-for-security-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:34:13 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/how-to-download-ipa-files-for-security-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Few weeks ago, I needed to download an iOS IPA file to perform a static analysis of that app. But as you may expect, Apple makes it extremely hard to download App Store to a destination that is not an iPhone/iPad, and if they are downloaded to an iPhone/iPad 📱 it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to extract the file. Unless the device is rooted, you are probably out of luck. So I searched and searched and searched for a method and finally found one using an open source package tool named IPATool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Atomic Red Team - A Purple Teaming Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/getting-started-with-atomic-red-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:34:13 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/getting-started-with-atomic-red-team/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What is Purple Teaming? For me, it simply means emulating attacker techniques and testing both your detection and response capabilities. Let&amp;rsquo;s say you are interested in T1136 and you want to confirm that your defenses are able to detect Account Creation. From a Purple Teaming prospective that means you should attempt to create local account(s) and check if your controls are able to detect (and respond) to this event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Pass SANS Exams</title>
      <link>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/how-to-pass-sans-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 01:52:54 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shellvenom.com/posts/how-to-pass-sans-exams/</guid>
      <description>When I was preparing for my GPEN exam, I searched online (a lot) to find some useful hints.
This article helps you in passing SANS/GIAC exams and get a high score. I&amp;rsquo;m going to share very simple and effective tips to help you archive that!
I myself have passed three GIAC exams as of today, I scored more than 90% in all three, and I finished ~30 minutes early ⚡ in each one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
